Hello everyone, welcome
to our seventh lecture
on respiratory physiology
and as a neuroscientist
this topic is very dear
to my heart because
it is on control
mechanisms of respiration.
I'm Dr. Jörg Litt Hest.
These session objectives are
consistent with the
event description
which is to focus on the
brainstem centers that
control respiration,
central and peripheral
sensors they utilize
and the mechanisms that
operate the effectors. To
integrate this knowledge,
the session features
specific situations in
which which respiratory
functions have to adapt
to higher oxygen demand
or lower oxygen supply.
This is the basic feedback
loop of respiratory control.
Let's begin with the
sensors in the lower left.
There are various kinds
of sensors that the
system employs. They're
either chemoreceptors
that react to chemicals or
they're mechanoreceptors
that react to
stretch, for instance.
The peripheral
chemoreceptors and those
for the respiratory
system are found in
the carotid bodies or
at the aortic arch.
And then there are central
chemoreceptors which
are found inside the
central nervous system.
The pulmonary
mechanoreceptors are all
associated with structures
of the lung itself
and are located within
the thoracic cavity.
All of these sensors
send information to the
respiratory control center,
which is located in the
medulla and overlaps into
the pons of the brainstem.
The respiratory control center
then sends out information
through the spinal
cord to the effectors.
The effectors are the
respiratory muscles,
and the largest of them is
of course the diaphragm.
This slide adds a
little more detail.
We can begin again
with the receptors,
so that's the aphoran
portion, so that's the portion
that brings information
into the central nervous
system. We have peripheral
chemoreceptors which are
located at the aortic arch
or at the carotid bodies.
They can sense oxygen,
carbon dioxide, and also pH.
This information is
related or relayed to
the brainstem via
cranial nerve 9 and 10.
There are central
chemoreceptors that
are inside the
brain which react to
pH, changes in pH
or hydrogen ions.
There are lung stretch
receptors, those are
mechanoreceptors that
information is relayed
to the brainstem via
cranial nerve 10.
And lastly, there are
muscle and joint receptors
which relay information
to the brainstem as well.
The key portion of the
medullary respiratory
center is the dorsal
respiratory group.
We're going to look at
this more in the coming
slides. This group is
influenced and functioned by
an apneustic center, which
is located in the pons.
And this type of
regulation is positive,
meaning that the
apneustic center initiates
a function in the dorsal
respiratory group.
In the pons, there's also
the pneumotoxic center,
and the pneumotoxic
center overall has an
inhibitory effect on the
dorsal respiratory group.
So, depending on all of this
interaction, Information
is then sent out to the
effectors, which, for instance,
is the diaphragm, but also
other respiratory muscles,
and this information travels
via the phrenic nerve.
This image depicts
the brainstem
centers that control breathing.
The most important of them
is the medullary respiratory
center that encompasses
various clusters of nuclei.
as you can see
here. It encompasses
the dorsal respiratory group,
it encompasses the pre
-Britzinger complex,
and also the ventral
respiratory group.
The dorsal respiratory group,
abbreviated DRG
in this lecture,
is involved in the
generation of inspiration
and also in the setting
of the respiratory rate.
This DRG works closely
together with the pneumotaxic
center, which is this
center up here in the pons,
which sends inhibitory signals,
but is also involved
in the regulation of
respiratory rate. So those
two, they work together.
The other respiratory
group that we have
here in the
medullary respiratory
center is the ventral
respiratory group.
And this respiratory
group is involved
in inspiration and
also in expiration,
but has its main function
in the expiratory sector.
This group is inactive
during quiet breathing.
So when only tidal
breathing occurs, there is
no firing from the
ventral respiratory group.
So forced breathing
events are different. So
that is when the ventral
respiratory group engages.
So forced inspiration
or forced expiration.
The pre-Bertzinger
complex is also involved
in rhythm generation,
so it also works
together with the dorsal
respiratory group by
inhibiting dorsal
respiratory group neurons.
Lastly, we have the
apneustic center, and
the apneustic center
sends positive signals to
the dorsal respiratory
group. and by doing
that it controls
breathing intensity so for
instance it controls
the depth of breathing
now all of these centers
they operate in reaction
to central chemoreceptors
so central chemoreceptors
are involved in minute
-to-minute breathing.
So that's the basic function
of the respiratory system,
the basic tidal function
of the respiratory system.
These sensors are nearby
the dorsal respiratory
group. The dorsal respiratory
group would just be
on the other side here. So
this, of course, depicts
the medulla and the
sensors in an area of the
medulla that's called the
ventrolateral medulla.
And there's a rostral,
almost forward cluster,
an intermediate one, and
a caudate receptor area.
The most important
of the chemoreceptors
are the central chemoreceptors,
and they can sense the
pH of the cerebrospinal
fluid directly and carbon
dioxide indirectly.
And I will take you
through now how this works.
So for instance, if
there's a buildup of
CO2 in capillary blood
going to the brain,
then the CO2, because
it's lipophilic,
can diffuse
into the medulla,
and from there
into the cerebrospinal fluid.
There, it joins the
bicarbonate buffer system on
the other side. As you
can see here, it has just
left the bicarbonate buffer
system on the capillary
end, and it rejoins the
bicarbonate buffer system
on the cerebrospinal
fluid end. And if there's
a lot of CO2, then that
pushes the conversion
towards carbonic acid and
lastly, bicarbonate. And
when bicarbonate forms,
then a hydrogen ion is
dissociated, and that is the
hydrogen that's sensed by
the central chemoreceptors.
So, in other words,
a buildup of carbon
dioxide, for instance,
through increased activity,
will result in the
formation or in the
dissociation of carbonic
acid and the formation
of hydrogen ions, which
can be sensed by the
central chemoreceptors.
Upon sensing a lower pH,
which is what this is,
the central chemoreceptors
will release serotonin,
that's a neurotransmitter
that these neurons use,
which will travel to the
inspiratory center, the DRG,
which will then elicit
hyperventilation in
response to high CO2
levels. and hyperventilation
is defined as the
increase of breathing
frequency and volume. So
this makes total sense.
We have a lot of activity,
a buildup of CO2,
the central chemoreceptors
sense a lower pH,
and then sending
information via serotonin
to the DRG, which
then increases the
frequency and the
volume of breathing.
Just as a remark,
the expiratory center in
the ventral respiratory
group uses GABA as
the neurotransmitter.
So we already talked about
the peripheral chemoreceptors.
They are sensitive to three
chemicals or gases, to
oxygen of course, carbon
dioxide, and also hydrogen
ions. And as I mentioned
before, they can be either
located in the carotid
bodies or they can be found
in the aortic arch, in the
so-called aortic bodies.
Depending on where they are.
There are different
cranial nerves that pick up
this information and sent
this to the brainstem. The
information that comes
from the aortic bodies
travels through the vagus
nerve, that's cranial nerve
10 of course, and the
sensor information that
originates from the
carotid bodies travels via
cranial nerve 9 which is
the glossopharyngeal nerve.
So what do they really sense
and how about
their sensitivity?
So the oxygen by these
peripheral chemoreceptors
has to be very low to
be sensed by them. So
actually the partial
pressure of oxygen has
to be equal or less to
60 millimeters mercury
in order to be sensed
and elicit a response.
The CO2 sensors, they're
actually less dominant
in the periphery because
we already have a very
dominant system that
senses CO2 indirectly that
we just went over in the
central nervous system.
Another thing that's
noteworthy is that the pH can
only be sensed by the
carotid bodies, because there
are no sensors for hydrogen
ions in the aortic arch.
Now, there are other
types of peripheral
receptors that can alter
breathing. They're,
for instance, the
irritant receptors.
They are mainly located
in the trachea or at the
bifurcation of the main
bronchi, as you can see
here. They can react to
certain chemicals, to dust,
to cold air, and their
role is to clear this area
and make sure that
nothing dislodges further
down the respiratory tree.
In order to do so, their
excitation will make us
cough, and it will also
cause bronchoconstriction
to squeeze stuff out.
Then there are muscle
and joint receptors,
and they are mainly found
in the muscles of the chest.
They sense muscle tension
and thereby they affect
breathing. So it's
like a sensory feedback
that tells our brainstem
and the respiratory
center in there, much about
the state of breathing
based on muscle function
or muscle tension.
There are stretch receptors
and they are mainly
found in the larger bronchi
and as you can see here,
and bronchioles, and they
sense lung inflation.
And the effect of
their sensation is to
stop further inflammation
of the lungs,
so they terminate
inflation of the lungs.
Now, this function is part
of a reflex that's been
very well studied and is
known as the herring borough
inflation reflex. So
that reflex that utilizes
these stretch receptors
basically inhibits overinflation
of our lungs because
the tissues are very
fragile and overinflation
would cause a lot of damage.
Then lastly, there are
so-called J receptors.
They are further down the
respiratory tree at the site
of the alveoli and ducts
leading into the alveoli.
J stands for
juxtacapillary receptors.
They can sense
chemicals, stretch,
and also they react
pulmonary edema.
And once they get
activated, they affect us to
shallow breathing to
prevent damage to those
structures. They will lead
to bronchoconstriction
for the same reason,
and also mucous
secretion. So these are
all defensive activities
that the sensation of
these receptors elicit.
It's believed, it's
not been conclusively
shown yet, but that
activation of the J receptors
is actually the main
reason for dyspnea
in patients with left
-sided heart failure.
Here are some breathing
patterns that I
would like you to
familiarize yourselves with.
I'm not going to read
this whole table,
but there are a few things
that I would like to point out.
So there's hypnea which is
indicates normal breathing
and normal breathing
pattern to you have already
heard about text tachypnea
which is indicates
increased respiratory rate
bradypnea which indicates
the opposite a decreased
respiratory rate apnea
means the absence of
breathing hyperpnea means
normal weight but deep
respirations, and so forth. So
you can follow the breathing
patterns that go with
each of these conditions
on the left-hand side.
The description will tell
you what they are and
will define them, and
here on the right you
have a list of causes or
conditions that elicit
those breathing patterns,
and this will become
very important for the
clinical portion or the
clinical coverage of
the respiratory system.
By keeping in mind the
regulation of the respiratory
system, the brainstem
centers that are involved
and the sensors and what they
sense, we can now explore
what happens during
activities such as exercise.
So exercise, of course,
utilizes large
muscles, which means
that oxygen
consumption goes up,
carbon dioxide production
goes up, and as a response
of the central chemoreceptors
that we looked at,
also ventilation
is upregulated.
Now what does this mean in
terms of arterial blood?
Well, for the most part,
there is no change in the
partial pressure of oxygen,
carbon dioxide, and pH.
So these two, carbon dioxide
and pH, they go together.
In certain extreme
cases of exercise,
the pH can drop a little bit.
What happens to venous
blood? Well, venous blood,
because of the
increased consumption of
energy and the production
of carbon dioxide,
the venous partial pressure of
carbon dioxide of
course goes up.
So how does the system react in
terms of pulmonary blood flow?
Well as a result of all of
this, the cardiac output
goes up because there is an
increased demand of oxygen
and an increased demand
for carbon dioxide removal
so the amount of blood
that hits the lungs for
reoxygenation and carbon dioxide
removal needs to be increased
and that's exactly what
happens here so the
ventilation rate goes up from
six or six to seven and a
half liters depends on the
text, to over 120 liters
per minute to facilitate
this and provide homeostasis
in the blood.
Then increased cardiac
output, of course,
is followed by increased
pulmonary blood flow. Remember
that both systemic and
pulmonary circulation move the
same amount blood and also
as a result the ventilation
to perfusion ratio is more
even across the lungs and
that is mainly achieved by
cutting out dead space so
there were poorly ventilated
areas at rest for instance
where ventilation was not
good and as a result through
hypoxic vasoconstriction
also blood supply was shifted
to other areas. Now, when
the demand is that high,
the ventilation to perfusion
ratio is very even across
the entire lungs, and there's
literally no dead space.
Another way to facilitate
this high level
of activity is to shift
the oxygen hemoglobin
dissociation curve.
You can see it here.
As a result, we
experience a right shift.
So right shift in this
case means that it gets
easier for oxygen to be
unloaded so the affinity
for oxygen goes down and
the p50 value goes up.
Another condition where
the respiratory system
has to go to extreme
lengths to ensure
homeostasis is the
adaption to high altitude.
So I looked it up and
you already know that the
partial pressure for oxygen
where we live is around
160 millimeters mercury.
On Mount Everest it's only 47.
So that's a severe
reduction which of
course comes with
hypoxic vasoconstriction,
and if not controlled,
can lead to death.
High altitude sickness comes
with these signs and symptoms,
so headache, fatigue,
dizziness, nausea,
palpitations, and insomnia are
most frequently reported.
again this whole situation
is due to the decreased
atmospheric pressure and
the decreased availability
of oxygen in the inspired
air which leads to a reduced
alveolar partial pressure
of oxygen well we kind
of already covered the
cause for pulmonary epoxic
vasoconstriction so what
happens to ventilation well
of course in this situation
the system is trying to
get to more oxygen so
the ventilation rate remember
the dot means rate goes
up leading to hyperventilation
at least initially
and the trigger for this
is a partial pressure of
oxygen of equal or less
than 60 millimeters mercury
So hyperventilation blows
off a lot of carbon dioxide
so you can see if
hyperventilation removes this
carbon dioxide and as a
result this entire bicarbonate
buffer system shifts to
the left therefore so these
components become less
and less and more CO2 is
being blown off and as a
result this hydrogen ion goes
away, leaving the body in
a respiratory alkalosis.
So that's one of the things
that can happen, plus the
partial pressure of oxygen,
of course, still remains
reduced because of the low
concentration in the air.
This alkalosis can be treated.
Here's one of the
drugs that can be used.
Zetazolamide.
Zetazolamide inhibits
carbonic anhydrase. So when
this is given, this part
of the bicarbonate buffer
system cannot turn into
water and be blown off as
carbon dioxide, which kind
of counterbalances the
respiratory alkalosis that
would be observed otherwise.
So what happens to
pulmonary blood flow.
Of course, pulmonary
blood flow increases.
That increase can be
significant and therefore
can significantly increase
pulmonary resistance.
That requires the
pulmonary artery
to go in with more pressure.
And if this situation
ensues or persists
for a longer amount of
time, then hypertrophy
of the right ventricle
that pumps blood
into the pulmonary
circulation can ensue.
In this situation,
the oxygen hemoglobin
dissociation curve shifts to
the right. So once again,
it ensures that oxygen
bound to hemoglobin becomes
more readily available.
It does that in responds
to increased 2,3-DPG.
Remember, that is an
intermediate of glycolysis.
And if you also remember
that glycolysis is anaerobic,
so glycolysis works
without oxygen, then it's
easy to imagine why a 2,3
-DPG goes up under hypoxic
conditions. So it's just
a way for the body to make
extra energy under
slightly anaerobic, or I
should not say anaerobic,
but hypoxic conditions.
So because glycolysis
is upregulated,
we see more 2,3-DPG
under hypoxic conditions.
So once again, the
P50 goes up, and as a
result of the right
shift, as I already
said, the affinity
for oxygen goes down.
So this decreased partial
pressure of oxygen leads to
hypoxia and the kidney and
in some cases to a smaller
degree the liver they can
sense this. They produce the
glycohormone erythropoietin
And then erythropoietin
leads to a condition of
polycythemia at high altitude,
and that is the increased
abundance of red blood cells.
Now, that's a good
thing in terms
of the oxygen
carrying capacity.
It's a bad thing because
blood that has abnormally
high levels of red blood
cells is also more viscous.
and also makes it
more difficult to
sustain or facilitate
pulmonary blood flow.
So there has to be a balance
between the two of them.
In the next two slides,
we're going to explore
the difference between
hypoxemia and hypoxia and
look at some details. The
general difference between
the two of them is that
hypoxemia indicates a
low partial pressure of
oxygen in arterial blood,
and hypoxia indicates low
partial pressure in the
tissues. So hypoxemia
can cause hypoxia, but
there are also other
reasons for hypoxia than
hypoxemia. So that's the
best way of looking at both.
So at high altitude,
let's start with our first
example. We have a low
partial pressure of
oxygen in the air that leads
to low partial pressure
of inspired oxygen.
And as a result, the
partial pressure of arterial
oxygen is decreased.
The alveolar to arterial
oxygen gradient is normal
because the diffusion is
not the problem here it's a
diffusion gradient so there's
too little in air and that
causes the problem but
diffusion is fine so therefore
the gradient is okay
therefore supplemental oxygen
is helpful because it
increases this capital a which
is alveolar oxygen content
it'll increase the driving
force of oxygen into the
system and remedy the issue.
Hypoventilation can cause a
low partial pressure of oxygen.
Yeah, so in hyperventilation,
the partial pressure
of oxygen is decreased. Also
here, the gradient between
alveolar and arterial
oxygen is normal because
once again the issue is
not the diffusion the issue
is not enough breathing
going on to bring in enough
oxygen and for the reason
of there not being a
physical barrier also supplemental
oxygen is helpful then
next we have diffusion
defects such as fibrosis
so fibrosis is indicative
of extra fibrotic tissue,
so that increases the
diffusion distance for oxygen
from alveolar into arterial
blood. For that reason,
the AA gradient is increased.
Also here, supplemental
oxygen is helpful.
It maxes out the
driving force of oxygen
into the system, and
that's what it'll do.
Hypoxemia due to ventilation
to perfusion defect
can also lead to low
arterial oxygen content.
An example would be zone
of west number one, so at
the apex of the lung, where
we have a lot of ventilation
and not enough perfusion,
and that would be an
example. So also here, the
AA gradient is increased
because the system, there's
a barrier in the system
that prevents the oxygen
from going from one
compartment, which is the
alveolus, into the arterial
system. And also here to
increase the driving force,
supplemental oxygen is helpful.
And then a few lectures
back, we looked at right
to left shunt that also
leads to decreased oxygen
content in arterial blood
mainly because a
mixing of oxygen poor
with freshly oxygenated
blood is going on
because of this the AA
gradient is increased and
And here I wrote that
supplemental oxygen
would be limited in
helpful function.
Yes, it can max out the
gradient, but because,
especially depending on
the size of the defect, in
most cases, the defect would
be overwhelming whatever
we would be able to do
with supplemental oxygen.
So that's why supplemental
oxygen is mostly
not that helpful. But I
can't fully rule it out
because it really depends
on the size of the
defect. So that's why
it says limited here.
As we have seen in the past
few years, COVID-19 also
has an effect on arterial
oxygen and it's decreased.
That's also the case with
some forms of long COVID
now that we see. So it's
become persistent. and so
also here the AA gradient
is increased because we
have an extra barrier in
this case it's not as with
fibrosis a tissue barrier
but it's a liquid barrier
so as a result of COVID
infection inflammation can
ensue that leads to
pulmonary flooding so it's an
edema of if you will And
that extra fluid increases
diffusion distance of
gases that need to diffuse.
And for that reason, the
AA gradient is increased.
Also here, to max out
diffusion pressure
of oxygen into the
system, supplemental
oxygen can definitely
be helpful.
Let's explore hypoxia. So
hypoxia, as I said before,
is defined as decrease of
oxygen delivery to tissues.
That's how it's different
than hypoxemia, which
just looks at the oxygen
content in arterial blood.
First of our examples
is cardiac output
decreased, leads to
decreased blood flow.
So of course that
affects target tissues.
They experience
hypoxia. However,
it does not translate
into a lower partial
pressure of arterial
oxygen because the blood
doesn't have enough
time to pick up gases.
And our next is hypoxemia.
So that is defined as
lower partial pressure of
oxygen in arterial blood,
therefore the downward
arrow in the next column.
Hypoxemia leads to lower
oxygen saturation of
hemoglobin because there's
just not enough oxygen
in the arterial blood
that can be looked at and
described as lowered
oxygen content of blood.
Next, we have anemia.
Anemia means reduced
amount of red
blood cells serving
the body because of
a reduction in red
blood cell content.
The oxygen carrying
capacity of the blood is
being reduced mainly
because with less red blood
cells, we also have
less hemoglobin, which
is our oxygen carrying
molecule and as i said
that lowers the oxygen
content of blood can you
guess why we don't have
a downward error here
well um just remember
that how we arrive at
partial pressures we're
only looking at dissolved
gases So, oxygen is 3D
dissolved in blood, and
also the portion of oxygen
that is dissolved in
part of the bicarbonate
buffer system counts.
But the oxygen that's bound
to hemoglobin and red blood
cells does not count in
determining the partial
pressure. Therefore, we don't
see a downward error here.
um carbon monocyte poisoning
leads to reduced oxygen
content of blood and a left
shift of the oxygen hemoglobin
curve so it binds competitively
to the binding side
of oxygen it binds very
tightly and if you remember
from from our previous lectures
tight binding of oxygen
to one of the four binding
sites increases the
affinity of the other sites
for oxygen and because carbon
monoxide binds so readily
we see a left shift so it
elicits that mechanism lastly
we have cyanide poisoning
so here what's affected is
the electron transport chain
so some of the protein
complexes that are part of
the electron transport chain
cannot do their job so the
oxygen content of blood is
fine but the target tissues
are unable to use that
oxygen that of course leaves
the partial pressure of
arterial oxygen unaffected
but nevertheless causes
hypoxia and another word style
question for you during
an experimental trial of
mechanical ventilation on an
anesthetized animal a research
The researcher temporarily
disables the ventilator
safety limits and delivers
a sudden, massive volume
of air that severely over
-inflates the animal's lungs.
The researcher observes
an immediate involuntary
arrest of the animal's
inspiratory effort
and a prolongation of
its expiratory phase.
Which of the following
pathways is responsible
for this protective
respiratory reflex?
choice a j receptors in
the alveolar walls detect
the stretch enter and
signal the spinal cord
to cause rapid shallow
gasping so what do j
receptors do by the way
that's they stand for
jerks the capillary
receptors and they can sense
chemicals that's what they
mainly do They can also
sense some stretch, which
allows them to also get
activated by pulmonary edema
because an overabundance
of fluids in the lungs
will also cause stretch.
And they will indeed
cause shallow breathing,
bronchial constriction,
and mucous secretion. So
none of those fit our
bill with this experiment.
How about carotid body
chemoreceptors that detect
the sudden stretch and
signal the apneustic
center in the pons to
promote gasping, that's B.
Well, carotid body
receptors are chemical
receptors and chemical
only, not stretch. And
they sense mainly hypoxia,
so lack of oxygen,
hypercapnium,
overabundance of CO2,
and also acidosis so
low ph and when they get
activated they will send
the glossopharyngeal
nerve which is cranial
nerve 9 which then sends
information to the nucleus
tractus solitarius and
that activation will lead
to a faster and deeper
breathing so that's also not
what we're observing here how
about the irritant receptors
in the trachea detect
the high pressure and trigger
an immediate prolonged
inspiratory gas to protect the
avio line well that already
sounds not what's
happening um these irritant
receptors are actually
specifically um sensing chemicals
um things in dust but also
temperature so and that
is to protect our lungs
from harmful substances
but also from the damage
that cold air in very
cold climates can do to
our respiratory parenchyma
and their effect is
coughing and also bronchial
constriction so reduction
of airway diameter
in a protective manner.
Then we have E. Those are
central chemoreceptors
in the fourth ventricle sense
the sudden lung inflation
and directly block phrenic
nerve firing at the
spinal level. Well, you
hopefully know and that
central chemoreceptors
are called central because
they're actually in the
brain. They are in the fourth
ventricle and um well one
can find them throughout
the fourth ventricle
and they primarily sense
hydrogen ion concentration
in cerebrospinal
fluid and that is as a
result of hypercapnia
so they do not directly
sense low oxygen levels
they sense low oxygen levels
indirect as a function
of high carbon dioxide
levels which can have its own
issues but that's how
they work and they're
triggering increases ventilation
so that's also not worth
preserving what we're
observing so we're left
here with c uh slowly
adapting pulmonary stretch
receptors in the airways and
smooth muscle sent inhibitory
signals via the vagus
nerve to the med medulla
to terminate inspiration
so that is um choice c
and um so those those cells
they're um responsible
to or their function
is to keep um stretch
away from lung parenchyma
to prevent damage
and the underlying reflex
that causes this is
also known as the herring
broyer inflation reflex
that information
then when these
cells get activated
is actually also
sent to the nucleus tractus
solitarius to the medulla
but this time that's being
done by cranial nerve 10
or the vagus nerve so c
is the correct answer here
Please take a
look at Constanzo.
You can access the book
through Clinical Keys and
each chapter in Constanzo's
has a really good
summary portion. All of
the main points that I've
made here are in one
way or the other in that
summary plus the self-quizzing
questions with answers
at the end of the book
are really good. They're
not medical board style
but you know we're really
looking for concepts um
and you definitely get
those out of uh interacting
with those questions
if you want to do it in
the most efficient way
find some friends to do
the questions with and
i think that's the best
way to handle this um
please remember that
we also use scholar rx
i've um added the
scholar x modules
that fit this topic
um and all of that
information you can
find in the CPG.
Lastly, I would be happy
about some feedback. If
you like this, if you
got something out of it,
let me know. If there
are things that you would
like different, let me
know too. And so thank
you very much and have a
great rest of your day.